Kloud:
Jurate: okay hello hello right okay I plan to show you I need the latest file.
Jurate: which one is your latest file?
Kloud: once again sorry you can call the next cloud and grab it but I can send it to you as a PDF or something.
Jurate: yeah and immediately as a PDF.
Jurate: it will be one moment and now I'm unable to find in a fast mode.
Jurate: just it will be quicker if you would send and I will tell you what has to be done in next steps and I will give you you know like samples of other bachelor thesis and I will send you print screens on what you need to do.
Kloud: yeah okay we have examples but they're like from 2007 or something.
Jurate: I have fresher ones even if they're in Lithuania.
Jurate: you will see the structure I do also have in English as well.
Jurate: it's just that I cannot give them to you due to privacy.
Jurate: yeah right yeah I just can't.
Jurate: I can.
Jurate: I can give you snapshots of it but I can't you give it whole?
Jurate: I mean yeah probably you will not share it but but still okay let me then share everything that I that I have.
Jurate: let's go with screens let's go live.
Jurate: okay right so I will send you a feedback regarding introduction because I have it on my iPad.
Jurate: so what will we?
Jurate: what do you do?
Jurate: usually in introductions we don't use these you know like bullet points because this is more of a requirements.
Jurate: okay so you can omit these like in general.
Jurate: we need to access this and this.
Kloud: so do I just omit or do I integrate them into like a normal flow of the text?
Jurate: it would be.
Jurate: it would be as a normal flow would be better not bullet list.
Jurate: okay you know like what should be done etc.
Jurate: etc.
Jurate: problem of the feces okay objectives more like aim of the feces.
Jurate: but I will send you the feedback.
Jurate: you don't have to do anything now.
Jurate: it's just like aim of the feces.
Kloud: it was in the template.
Kloud: I just copied it.
Jurate: yeah yeah but it's better to like aim and then we have either objectives or tasks.
Jurate: it would be better okay formulate it like this and this is enough like this.
Jurate: okay your objective.
Jurate: okay aim that that's it.
Jurate: you don't have to write it in two sentences is usually one.
Jurate: what I'm trying to do and why am I doing this?
Jurate: this one is good dynamical and auxiliary features and features and integrations.
Jurate: omit this completely because first is like you're analyzing existing solutions for that.
Jurate: okay yeah yeah like various websites mobile apps etc.
Jurate: etc.
Jurate: your second task should be technology web technology analyze existing technologies used for web development.
Jurate: it's more like okay but you are developing your.
Kloud: it's not well it's like app so it's like for cross platform development.
Jurate: then yeah I'm just giving an example like if let's say it would be a web app.
Jurate: so I need to specify if it's a cross-platform application.
Jurate: then you need to analyze technologies because this second chapter is to prove that the technology stack that you have decided to work with and that it's plausible mm-hmm even though you already are working.
Jurate: I mean it's a little bit of cheating I call it but you still need to show that you at least know other existing alternatives.
Jurate: yeah you still need to demonstrate that you did analysis because you did.
Jurate: I mean it just.
Jurate: it's not just described.
Jurate: yeah so that so that you would not have this argument as I've heard some students say.
Jurate: why did you choose Spring Boot?
Jurate: because I know Java and I like Java and it was easier and the committee was like oh come on can you at least make something on the spot that is not so lame basically like this.
Jurate: so you need the second chapter now your determined core and auxiliary features and design a cross-platform application.
Jurate: it's exactly the same.
Jurate: so you just keep the third one.
Jurate: just design and develop because when you are designing you're already determining based on the previous analysis what should be in your developed system.
Jurate: so this design design.
Jurate: you can actually have this design across platform which is going to be 2 plus 3 your current second and third in the world.
Jurate: and yeah and then develop yeah then this one is going to develop and test the solution.
Jurate: okay now these implement changes in the location of the feedback.
Jurate: you can do it.
Jurate: you can have this fifth task which is improvements.
Jurate: that one keep it but this is not necessary.
Jurate: gather feedback from real users.
Jurate: this is going to be your final one gather the feedback and improve the proposed solution the developed solution or something like this.
Jurate: so you will have two tasks that are from theory existing solutions and technology analysis.
Jurate: then your first the third task is going to be like modeling designing that system the set system fourth is going to be developed and test and your task number five is going to be get feedback and improve based on on that feedback like this.
Kloud: and one question I have with the task as well do the topics at the bottom like further down have to match those exactly.
Kloud: or is it just like an overview and the topics will can be a bit different?
Jurate: what do you mean top top topics what topics you mean?
Kloud: I mean the chapters chapters.
Jurate: yeah yeah yes they have to.
Jurate: they have to answer these tasks but the type the naming is going to be different.
Jurate: okay for example if you're analyzing existing solutions you know like from other universities evaluate their feature set it's okay.
Jurate: so your one first big chapter is going to be for task one and for task number two.
Jurate: so your chapter one is going to be like how to covering to two tasks.
Jurate: okay yeah first chapter is going to have some kind of a title that encompasses both of these such as I'm improvising okay like campus management solutions and cross-platform development something like this.
Jurate: and then your chapter one point one is going to be campus existing campus management systems and one point one one is going to be option one one one two is going to be option two etc.
Jurate: etc.
Jurate: then you will have one point two chapter which is going to be cross-platform development technologies and then you will have one two one let's say front end one two two is going to be let's say back end one two three like server side solution solution something like this.
Jurate: maybe one two four is going to be database something like this.
Jurate: okay understood yeah so it's going to be like this and your whole chapter one answers everything that is related to theory and basically one point one will answer your first question and one point two will answer your second question.
Jurate: right so if I'm going to scroll this one is good work area.
Jurate: you don't even have to write this one you can just have it as a you know introductory one or two pages something like this.
Jurate: not necessarily this is too short I would actually say because working area is usually one to two pages.
Kloud: okay so this is less than one page and this also mirrors the the things I've wrote in the previous chapters a bit.
Kloud: so I'm not sure if this is okay.
Jurate: yeah so basically what you're doing?
Jurate: you are describing what is in going to be in the following chapters.
Jurate: you can expect this working area by including references to scientific papers and whereas statistical data how I would imagine you could add more information to this one the basically to this not paragraph not in a chapter.
Jurate: this is like intro.
Jurate: introductory text is by starting like from a very far point of view like giving an overall idea such as worldwide.
Jurate: basically universities accept students from all the countries okay and this results in the fact that depending on the country people come with certain expectations and certain practices.
Jurate: okay let's say if I go to United States I will probably dislike the system because in my opinion it's too lax and maybe not structured enough.
Jurate: okay those who come from example from Nigeria what we have in our university is a hardcore like very strict and let's say a set of rules that we have and that is familiar to us.
Jurate: it's not familiar to students and then they get lost.
Jurate: okay like when to attend lectures how to organize work multiple systems.
Jurate: basically this results in a confusion okay and in the fact that maybe time and information is not managed efficiently for the student.
Jurate: okay so this is your introductory area and this is why it's important to have this universal like system that you are trying to develop but basically the need for such systems which are easy to access which are intuitive which are clear and that they work efficiently with whatever is provided in that university.
Jurate: that's why it's important.
Jurate: this is your work area.
Jurate: okay like like this.
Kloud: okay so I start from that.
Kloud: do I continue like I continued like I wrote here.
Jurate: I will probably slightly minimize the text like in less detail but you will keep part of this text for sure.
Jurate: okay and then you will continue like in the following chapters.
Jurate: you usually you'd never say that you never talk in the first person.
Jurate: so it's going to be like following chapters analyze the mentioned systems their pros and cons.
Jurate: okay then technology stack analysis is going to be presented in chapter 1.2 something like this like you have this intro the structure and then you continue working basically defining or reviewing similar systems like official Moodle app.
Jurate: yeah with print screens old Vilnius mobile app etc.
Jurate: etc.
Jurate: so what is important?
Kloud: yeah how exactly do I like structure those parts?
Jurate: okay I can.
Jurate: I can actually show you a an example of existing bachelor thesis.
Jurate: I mean what you did.
Jurate: very good I mean this is what you're going to analyze now.
Jurate: you need to just need to structure it.
Jurate: so okay an example on how to do this.
Jurate: let me quickly show you.
Jurate: okay for example this is like two years ago.
Jurate: this is a student's work again.
Jurate: he was also from English speaking group.
Jurate: I can show you the way he structures.
Jurate: so what he did?
Jurate: he developed a dormitory management mobile app because as a foreign student he got annoyed like how the hell am I supposed to know where to live?
Jurate: should I go to Arroyo de Salte?
Jurate: inconvenient expensive if I live in a dormitory I need to write to administrators.
Jurate: administrators maybe they will write you back maybe not.
Jurate: payment system is like manual pretty much you pay then you send the payment confirmation.
Jurate: inconvenient.
Jurate: so what he wanted?
Jurate: he wanted to develop an Android app like a prototype mm-hmm.
Jurate: so so this is the relevance.
Jurate: let's go.
Jurate: so this is the introduction.
Jurate: yeah like for example his first chapter is like accommodation management and it's the and its importance.
Jurate: and here we have accommodation reservation systems and let's say it's booking.com because this is what works for students as well.
Jurate: and he begins describing like what is booking how popular it is and what it offers.
Jurate: okay and then he goes like with print screen.
Jurate: so if you're defining some kind of like what it offers you need to add.
Jurate: I recommend to adding print screens with main functions.
Jurate: okay.
Jurate: so if you let's say you're analyzing some kind of web app and it's like a huge chunky page you don't have to add like front front page print screen because it's pointless.
Jurate: yeah but what you can do?
Jurate: you can print screen certain areas with certain functionality that you think is very good for example that is relevant to the thing?
Jurate: yeah not not not all but like several relevant and all the others are going to be provided in the text.
Jurate: so over here what he did is like you know super convenient short info like a picture that lies and then a description a picture that lies and then a description and I how to view information because he thinks this is cool because he wanted to do something similar like an overview.
Jurate: then I'm choosing a dormitory then I'm choosing the room and then what should I do with payment something like this.
Jurate: and then he provides like a functionality what it offers.
Jurate: I think this is not the final version.
Jurate: so you provide what is good and then you write down for example maybe things that it's lacking.
Jurate: then he goes for Airbnb exactly the same like short description what it does like an overall and then he goes into details and again how how it's structured what is important?
Kloud: okay and what are those?
Kloud: what are those references like six and five to what?
Jurate: to the web page to the web page the bottom to the website.
Jurate: understood yes yes yes yes and in the references in these sources that you have I'm going to scroll down for example here reference six like access.
Jurate: one is accessed online etc.
Jurate: just like a source because it's not it's not your print screen it's not your developed system.
Jurate: so all these things websites they're going to be as a reference.
Jurate: the same with Airbnb and for example what is good?
Jurate: and then we have despite being globally available it has some issues and he writes them down.
Jurate: then we have our what the Sultan again how to find something something and again compared to others what it has what it doesn't have and so on.
Jurate: and then we have universities official web page mm-hmm.
Jurate: so it's fitting that he added a web page because it doesn't have anything.
Jurate: it's like a proof here.
Jurate: yeah there's a there's an email.
Jurate: that's it fail.
Jurate: I mean we have a chatbot.
Jurate: it doesn't help me.
Jurate: something like that.
Jurate: okay and the same with Vilnius University something like this.
Jurate: that's it.
Jurate: this is how you struck.
Jurate: okay like okay begin start describing what the task.
Jurate: insert some kind of print screens with in your case in relevant useful for example features.
Jurate: then you continue the describing the text.
Jurate: why is it formatted in this way?
Jurate: it's just that all your images must be mentioned in the text first.
Jurate: so it goes like this you start describing.
Jurate: then you say for example this app has these these decent features as shown in figure why ABC etc.
Jurate: insert pictures and then you continue describing like this.
Jurate: and then pros cons and etc.
Jurate: then 1.2 chapter as I've said because you need to have technology overview.
Jurate: so he was working with.
Jurate: his bachelor thesis was was about Android app development.
Jurate: so what he did?
Jurate: he started like fundamentals of app development.
Jurate: you might argue maybe these are like basic stuff but as bachelor great students you don't have to begin immediately you know with scientific paper review.
Jurate: it's okay if you give this broader of overview like how mobile apps that are developed in general.
Jurate: so he specifies you know like what are the approaches and then he chooses like one approach that he will work with something like this.
Jurate: but the analysis is done this application cycle not necessary.
Jurate: but what he does?
Jurate: he goes with Android then he analyzes Apple iOS in his case and then he goes Kotlin yeah Kotlin.
Jurate: then he not compared with Java and something like this.
Jurate: then he goes for requirement specification.
Jurate: in my opinion this section could have been broader and this is where I will show you a Lithuanian work because in my opinion it's better to have more things.
Jurate: so what the student did here?
Jurate: he developed a web platform.
Jurate: okay and he was interested in learning methods for students in school.
Jurate: so what he did?
Jurate: he provided because this he already had his own like learning system what he wanted to implement he wanted to implement like how to prepare for tests exams using a certain card methods like it's from pedagogy car from that area.
Jurate: so he wanted to apply and digitalize this idea.
Jurate: so again what he did?
Jurate: I mean don't don't don't worry if it's an if it's on Lithuanian the structure is the same.
Jurate: so he has these learning platforms which are using interval flashcards.
Kloud: yeah I know I use them.
Jurate: yeah yeah.
Jurate: so he goes with okay yes how it does it what it has and then we have these prevalent which is pros.
Jurate: then he has these cons like this done.
Jurate: then he goes and analyzes quizlet okay okay the same situation yes same it's important to maintain the same structure study go exactly the same memorize exactly the same.
Jurate: so you already understand this section is clear.
Jurate: yeah this one is not necessary because he was from a program engineering course.
Jurate: so they are required to have this additional criteria table.
Jurate: so you can skip on this one.
Jurate: this is all you need a comparison table something.
Jurate: okay yeah it's like a comparison table based on the criteria that he deems useful.
Jurate: you can do it but it's not necessary for you.
Jurate: okay then we have a web system development technologies and he goes one the first one server side programming languages and he describes like PHP JavaScript Python Java because he's choosing among them and that's it like short with references what they offer how they're good and then he provides like a short description based on the analysis.
Jurate: I decided to choose PHP because and that's it provide argumentation.
Jurate: then we have web frameworks frameworks.
Jurate: yeah web frameworks and again frameworks etc.
Jurate: etc.
Jurate: no car get no framework.
Jurate: and again based on this analysis it was decided to do this and this.
Jurate: then we have UI frameworks so these are front-end okay basically and again Laravel a page render not sure if that's how in English.
Jurate: then we have angular view JS and again based on analysis I chose this.
Jurate: and then we have relational databases and again what databases he decided to analyze analysis and what was chosen.
Jurate: that's it?
Kloud: okay yeah that's it.
Kloud: I think I was kind of the same structure.
Kloud: this make no sense.
Jurate: yeah you because it's it's clear it's clean and actually provides your ability to you know gather and describe data.
Jurate: another thing that students are recommended to do and that they sometimes do.
Jurate: let me quickly open another students work it's this year students.
Jurate: again he is developing a tutor system.
Jurate: it's like his own business.
Jurate: he's tutoring and he's not satisfied with lesson management and the calendar and he's implementing you know certain backend solutions for his own like business.
Jurate: so what he does?
Jurate: yeah he's.
Jurate: he says basically I already have you know like tutors I'm also a tutor.
Jurate: I already have some kind of system.
Jurate: oh but it's not enough anymore because the business grew.
Jurate: so again he analyzes existing tutoring platforms.
Jurate: what functionalities do they offer so that he would understand what he wants to have in his own system.
Jurate: scroll scroll scroll what you can do.
Jurate: you can add comparative tables.
Jurate: for example here we have existing tutor tutoring system comparison where basically he says functionality property and then first second and third like candidates that he analyzed.
Jurate: and then he says for example lesson type individual group individual so that he would.
Jurate: basically he's systemizing the data.
Jurate: then we have like disciplines.
Jurate: how many subjects like only math eight disciplines more than 50 disciplines.
Jurate: account creation only administrator only administrator individual registration like as a user I can create it I don't have to contact you know that tutor those tutors so that they would create an account and basically what he did.
Jurate: he already decided on what features he would like to have and then describes what others are offering.
Jurate: so you can have something like this.
Kloud: so like the previous example but instead of the key are whatever.
Kloud: what was there on the left actual features on the left?
Jurate: I see yeah yeah something like this.
Jurate: you can you can have it.
Jurate: yes yes instead of this some students also do like for example he describes in here others do for example multiple lessons and then he has plus minus plus minus.
Jurate: you can also do it like in this manner.
Jurate: it's just that you don't have to have additional table with requirement one and then other table requirement one plus minus plus minus.
Jurate: you can have one table.
Jurate: yeah okay something like this.
Jurate: then he analyzes technologies technologies and then again you he provides technology overview.
Jurate: yeah comparison it's like where to use pros and cons like a summary table.
Jurate: you can also have this one not necessary but you can have if you think that it's it's better and it brings in clarity.
Kloud: something like this it will increase page count.
Jurate: yeah yes my god your priorities.
Jurate: but yeah yes yes how to generate pages at print screens and tables.
Jurate: yes but again don't don't expand too much because your literature analysis only literature when you start counting from chapter number one it should not exceed more than 20 pages because your bachelor thesis is up to 65 pages can be maybe 70 pages but no more.
Jurate: okay it doesn't have to be too long right?
Jurate: so when you are done with this you will go to chapter number two which is your system already design specification.
Jurate: you will definitely begin with a use case diagram what is your system and what your system allows to do?
Jurate: so you will have a use case with a table like like this.
Jurate: one main tasks because you will need to define functional requirements and functional requirements are mapped to use case.
Kloud: yeah okay yeah.
Jurate: so if you have some kind of use case such as for example based on let's say users can view their upcoming homeworks you know immediate integration from model just an example right?
Jurate: yeah.
Jurate: so in order to implement this feature this one use case it is entirely possible that you will have for example five functional requirements that you need to implement that are going to be mapped to exactly the same use case.
Jurate: I mean for this to work I need to do this this this and this like that.
Jurate: that's why it's important to have numbers and description.
Jurate: okay then you will have not necessary to have this flow diagram.
Jurate: what you will have you will have after that sequence diagrams basically sequence diagram so that you would explain how your use case is going to work.
Kloud: so you will have so here user why why?
Kloud: then maybe model API and then whatever?
Jurate: okay yeah so explain this is a simplified version.
Jurate: when you are going to work you are going to work with hold on hold on.
Jurate: this one is advanced level because we have a sub use cases.
Jurate: yeah sequence diagrams should be like this okay where you consider alternative and optional functionality if there is any okay so alternatives are going to be.
Jurate: for example you send the data and something fails so you will have site success route and fail route.
Jurate: so you need to add them into these diagrams to simplify.
Jurate: basically if you have five use cases you usually you have five sequence diagrams explaining each use case.
Jurate: if your use case is not complicated for example login and registration you can combine them into one diagram and show how login works and in the same diagram after that how registration works.
Jurate: okay like this okay yeah you can combine these and basically you will have description diagram description diagram.
Jurate: let's scroll down a little bit more like this this this this this oh Jesus Christ I need to stop this person already.
Jurate: this is already too much.
Jurate: yeah yeah.
Jurate: and then here you have.
Jurate: you will have a table with functional requirements like requirement description priority use case and dependencies because it's entirely possible that your functional requirements are going to be connected to other requirements such as this requirement is not going to be implemented if my other requirement is not implemented.
Jurate: oh you know they're connected.
Kloud: yeah okay so like this.
Jurate: so you will have functional requirements and then you will have non-functional requirements.
Jurate: so basically you will have one table of non-functional requirements.
Jurate: you don't have to provide details like priorities and severity and other stuff.
Jurate: they basically you will have a number description and the type for example reliability scalability development environment and etc.
Jurate: like this.
Kloud: so in my case I don't have a background.
Kloud: so no reliability or whatever requirement use.
Kloud: how do I say it?
Kloud: ease of use or something.
Kloud: can this be not functional?
Jurate: can you give me an example?
Jurate: I mean these requirements function non-functional requirements.
Jurate: there's actually a list.
Jurate: you don't have to include all of them.
Jurate: okay yeah it's based on what you need because usually non-functional requirements.
Jurate: there is actually a list.
Jurate: I can.
Jurate: I can find you these non-functional requirements.
Jurate: you will basically go through the list you will have examples and you will see.
Jurate: yeah I can apply this.
Jurate: no I cannot.
Kloud: oh there is a little.
Jurate: okay yeah yes there's a list.
Jurate: yes yes yes.
Jurate: for example let's say one of your requirements which is going to be I think it's compatibility for example that your developed system is going to work on let's say Chrome or Edge and Safari some kind of versions.
Jurate: okay if you would develop some kind of computer game you could say that this system works on Linux works on Windows and that's it and I'm not going to be bothered that it works on Mac as well.
Jurate: so these are non-functional requirements.
Jurate: okay yeah yeah yeah just like this for example in your case for example that your system is reliable and works 98 percent of the time and if some kind of crash happens that your system is going to be up and running within the given timeframe something like this.
Jurate: okay it's not necessary to add this.
Jurate: or for example that your system supports I don't know 1,000 users at the same time and it doesn't crash.
Jurate: something like this.
Kloud: yeah because my system would depend on the university's back and so this is basically requirements for the universities back end.
Jurate: yeah yeah yeah so basically universities back.
Jurate: so so in this case you don't even need to write this because this is not of your not your problem.
Jurate: okay not an issue something like this okay.
Jurate: so at this time you don't have to write neither functional nor non-functional requirements.
Jurate: basically what you need to do?
Jurate: you need to structure your analytical part first and try to create your use case.
Jurate: these are the steps that you need to take now.
Kloud: yeah okay understood is it?
Jurate: is it clearer now?
Kloud: yeah that's clear that's yeah yeah.
Jurate: so try this and again I will grab from the system your your your file.
Jurate: I imagine that you can improve.
Jurate: so far don't do anything with with introduction.
Jurate: concentrate on your chapter number one and try to answer these questions.
Jurate: well basically what we discussed now and I imagine that until next Friday you can provide like a draft version I mean draft not complete complete draft but like already structured version with not necessarily a beautiful text.
Jurate: but you can provide this until the next Friday.
Jurate: yeah that's chapter number one.
Jurate: and then you will begin with chapter number two.
Jurate: so if it's going to be 21st until 28th if we have yeah until 28th then you will begin your requirements.
Jurate: so until December number five you will have a draft version of your second chapter.
Jurate: then you will polish until December 12 your second chapter and then until 19th you will beautify both chapter one introduction and chapter number two.
Kloud: okay okay we have a bit different deadlines from our it's my understanding.
Jurate: what I want is just until 19th.
Jurate: I would like you to have the structure for chapter one and number two.
Jurate: okay it's not necessarily going to be beautiful.
Jurate: I know that you have your own timetable suggests that I'm asking you to do this until 19th so that you would go to holidays and not be bothered.
Jurate: okay because your BD1 is mainly from your chapter number one.
Jurate: but if you have already chapter number two even if it's not complete it's a huge plus.
Jurate: you will definitely get an approval.
Jurate: yeah I mean when it's going to be BD1 your your work has to be beautiful.
Jurate: whatever you present.
Jurate: it has to be like a final version already.
Jurate: nice beautiful text normal formatting all the references and etc.
Jurate: okay yeah I know that you have different timetables.
Kloud: they're shorter.
Kloud: they're like before before the December.
Kloud: I think we have to provide one moment mm-hmm.
Kloud: let me go into the mood and hope it doesn't ask me to log in.
Kloud: it will definitely ask me to log in.
Jurate: I know the same for me.
Jurate: even although I logged in not so long ago I still need to log in again because let's say I'm doing that from another computer which is bothersome.
Jurate: oh my god still it's less annoying than whatever Microsoft is doing.
Jurate: oh yeah okay yeah maybe it's it's less annoying although we do use my.
Jurate: we do use Microsoft though but but but still whatever Microsoft is doing there with at least at least the password that I enter in my work works because if it's a personal account you know there's a running joke.
Jurate: you know you entered your password.
Jurate: password is incorrect.
Jurate: please change your password.
Jurate: yeah change the password.
Jurate: password is incorrect.
Jurate: oh my goodness change the password.
Jurate: password cannot be the same as the password before although you have just entered this and then you just table flip and you say oh screw this.
Kloud: yeah.
Kloud: so here once theoretical part draft until November 27 he wants practical part draft until Thursday December 4th.
Kloud: so they're like you're saying I should complete the theory part until some.
Kloud: well for December what you said 13 of December yeah like like completely beautiful like full final version.
Jurate: I don't think you need to have this whole final version for your but I mean if if you're if you're if your subject requires.
Jurate: then yeah you do for the deadline for that deadline.
Jurate: but these deadlines are for me understood.
Kloud: this is this is what you want.
Jurate: but he wants that okay I see.
Kloud: hmm interested draft as I understand draft for him is like not beautiful.
Kloud: so just so.
Jurate: introduction draft.
Jurate: okay okay theoretical part draft.
Jurate: so you already presented this not presented.
Kloud: I just applauded.
Kloud: area and then some basic feedback.
Jurate: just some basic feedback.
Kloud: okay your feedback is better my feedback is better.
Kloud: yeah he gave something generic like let me see.
Jurate: well he does have a lot of students.
Kloud: oh yeah hey he said what the introduction should contain and that the thesis need to be provided in the past form.
Kloud: that's it okay.
Jurate: so yeah it is presented it is done.
Jurate: so these are like Jen general.
Jurate: yeah okay then you have practical part draft.
Jurate: so it's Wednesday 19th of November.
Jurate: so wait no it's due.
Kloud: yeah what also I don't understand.
Jurate: oh it's a draft oh my goodness.
Jurate: no no no it's okay you you look.
Jurate: okay it's 27th for the draft so it's very close to what I want.
Jurate: okay so fine until 27th beautify and add these all these things that I told you like.
Kloud: okay yeah I wanted to do it this weekend so should be okay.
Jurate: so yeah so if you have questions you can immediately ping me so that I could look at that work and I will immediately tell you what needs to be added.
Jurate: maybe okay so practical draft until December 4th still counts because you will also do that.
Jurate: okay it's just that until 27th try to prepare use case.
Jurate: okay mm-hmm include this.
Jurate: okay if these are the deadlines implementation draft is going to be Thursday 11th of December.
Jurate: so okay not too difficult not too difficult.
Jurate: he wants to do everything until December.
Jurate: he moved them see several times but it's a draft but it's a draft version and not the final.
Jurate: yes because with me you will have like a final version of chapter 1 and 2 will mostly final version until December 5 19th like before going to vacation you will do.
Jurate: you will do more than it's required over here for your homework tasks.
Jurate: mmm okay okay okay okay then complete until 27th.
Jurate: okay after this weekend basically concentrate on analysis and use case.
Jurate: okay yeah and then we will.
Jurate: we will contact again and you will start working on chapter number two.
Jurate: yeah if you want I can.
Jurate: I can send you print screens
Kloud: green screens yeah maybe yeah okay
Jurate: okay I can give you an example like how to you know tables summary tables how to organize use case plus what should be the table for those use cases and an example of sequence diagram so that you could get the basic idea.
Kloud: okay I have.
Kloud: okay yeah thanks.
Jurate: okay nice I have it.
Jurate: just I will.
Jurate: I will send these print screens in the evening.
Kloud: okay yeah that that's fine with me.
Kloud: yeah that's fine with me.
Jurate: okay any more questions?
Kloud: yeah I have a question about the references.
Kloud: so do I have to include some kind of like there is?
Kloud: is there a minimum for the references I should do and do they have to be scientific or at least 20 references?
Jurate: okay that's what I require.
Jurate: format from my students at least 20 references and if you're working with me so it's going to be five purely scientific papers and other ones are going to be books blogs documentation and websites.
Jurate: okay then yes concentrate on this at least five scientific papers.
Jurate: usually bachelor students are not required but all those who fall under my supervision they are required to do that.
Jurate: it's just because their work is going to be way more sophisticated and it demonstrates your ability to analyze but difficult material.
Jurate: yeah okay yeah so that's it.
Jurate: and then I will wait for your questions and you will wait for my print screens until the evening.
Kloud: yeah all right thank you again.
Jurate: okay okay see ya.
Kloud: yeah see you.